<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Universal</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Universal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Copyright (c) 2016 - 2018, Visible Data Ltd; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>other-project</title>
      <link>/projects-folder/other-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects-folder/other-project/</guid>
      <description> Hello Worls </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>statesRcontiguous</title>
      <link>/projects-folder/statesrcontiguous/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects-folder/statesrcontiguous/</guid>
      <description>statesRcontiguous A useful package for demonstrating choropleth please and more</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello R Markdown</title>
      <link>/blog/2015/07/23/2018-01-30-visible-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 21:13:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2015/07/23/2018-01-30-visible-setup/</guid>
      <description>R Markdown This is an R Markdown document. Markdown is a simple formatting syntax for authoring HTML, PDF, and MS Word documents. For more details on using R Markdown see http://rmarkdown.rstudio.com.
You can embed an R code chunk like this:
summary(cars) ## speed dist ## Min. : 4.0 Min. : 2.00 ## 1st Qu.:12.0 1st Qu.: 26.00 ## Median :15.0 Median : 36.00 ## Mean :15.4 Mean : 42.98 ## 3rd Qu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Visible Data is a consultancy and technical training company focusing on data science, data visualisation and reproducability based in Oxford, UK. It&amp;rsquo;s also a blog where our team share stories about their work and datasets that interest them. If you&amp;rsquo;d like to get in touch the best way to do that is emailing contact@visibledata.co.uk.
A note on the name, Visible Data is all about making data more accessible and reproducibly available to bridge what is often called the &amp;ldquo;data gap&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consultancy</title>
      <link>/consultancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/consultancy/</guid>
      <description>Visible Data provides consultancy services in data science, visualisation and advising on reproducible research and collaborative development practices. We&amp;rsquo;re currently working on a number of exciting projects which we&amp;rsquo;re looking forward to documenting here.
We&amp;rsquo;re primarily based in Oxford and would be pleased to discuss potential new projects, please do email us at contact@visibledata.co.uk
In the meantime, please do refer to our projects and training pages.
   OxShef: dataviz OxShef: dataviz is an ambitious partnership between University of Oxford and University of Sheffield to promote and support the development of reproducible interactive visualisations for communicating research datasets and outputs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>These are projects that the folks at Visible Data are currently working on, both within Visible Data and broader afield.
    OxShef: dataviz OxShef: dataviz is an ambitious partnership between University of Oxford and University of Sheffield to promote and support the development of reproducible interactive visualisations for communicating research datasets and outputs. The collaboration was co-founded by Martin John Hadley, Jez Cope, Anna Krystalli, Tim Snow, and Howard Noble.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects (projects.md)</title>
      <link>/projects-folder/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects-folder/projects/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m content/projects/projects.md I have some content here foo
description = &amp;ldquo;Frequently asked questions&amp;rdquo; keywords = [&amp;ldquo;FAQ&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;How do I&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;questions&amp;rdquo;,&amp;ldquo;what if&amp;rdquo;]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training</title>
      <link>/training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/training/</guid>
      <description>Visible Data offers one-on-one and group training courses on a variety of topics in data science and reproducible research methods. This page provides details on training courses recorded by folks working at Visible Data and how you can contact us to arrange custom training courses.
 Upcoming Courses Visible Data run a variety of courses across the UK, Europe and online that you can find in our embedded Google Calendar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>